<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Thank You</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Спасибо</string>
    <string name="main_text">Thank you for supporting us!\n\nDrop us a line at \n hello@simplemobiletools.com,\n we\'d love to hear all your feedback and suggestions.\n\nIn case you want to support us even more, there are multiple other ways of donating at https://simplemobiletools.com/donate\n\n(Please keep the app installed to avoid seeing the \'Purchase\' dialog and have all app features unlocked)</string>
    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="hide_launcher_icon">Скрыть значок приложения</string>
    <string name="hide_launcher_icon_explanation">Чтобы значок снова появился, вам потребуется переустановить приложение. Не волнуйтесь, ещё раз платить не придётся.</string>
    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Thank You — поддержавшим нас</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Спасибо вам за поддержку!</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        If you like our apps which are free, non-intrusive and have no ads, please consider supporting us in some way. It will be hugely appreciated.

        Having this app installed will prevent the displaying of a "Donate please" dialog in the free apps. Other than that, it also allows using a Shared Theme, which means that as soon as you change a color in one app, all other apps will be updated. Newly installed apps from the suite will automagically receive the shared colors too.

        It might unlock more extra features in the future. Please keep the app installed at least for a day, to avoid getting automatically refunded.

        This app is not a a replacement for the Pro app versions. You will still have to purchase them separately, in case you want to use them.

        Contains no ads or unnecessary permissions. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>
    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>