<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Thank You</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Thank You</string>
    <string name="main_text">Thank you for supporting us!\n\nDrop us a line at \n hello@simplemobiletools.com,\n we\'d love to hear all your feedback and suggestions.\n\nIn case you want to support us even more, there are multiple other ways of donating at https://simplemobiletools.com/donate\n\n(Please keep the app installed to avoid seeing the \'Purchase\' dialog and have all app features unlocked)</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="hide_launcher_icon">Hide the launcher icon</string>
    <string name="hide_launcher_icon_explanation">To have the launcher icon displayed again, you will have to reinstall the app. Don\'t worry, you won\'t have to pay again.</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">A paid app for people who want to support us.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        If you like our apps which are free, non-intrusive and have no ads, please consider supporting us in some way. It will be hugely appreciated.

        Having this app installed will prevent the displaying of a "Donate please" dialog. Other than that, it also allows using a Shared Theme, which means that as soon as you change a color in one app, all other apps will be updated. Newly installed apps from the suite will automagically receive the shared colors too.

        It might unlock more extra features in the future. Please keep the app installed at least for a day, to avoid getting automatically refunded.

        Contains no ads or unnecessary permissions. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors.

        This app is just one piece of a bigger series of apps. You can find the rest of them at https://www.simplemobiletools.com
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
